William Tjang

Email: william.tj29@gmail.com
Website: https://twillij.github.io/

I am a passionate game developer with over 3 years of experience programming in native C++, and about 2 years using Unreal Engine. I also have experience using C# and Unity in a non-professional capacity. I shipped my first title on PC and consoles as the lead publishing developer in 2022.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages C++, C#, HTML/CSS

Programming Environments Unreal Engine, Unity, Visual Studios, JetBrains Rider

Game Development Gameplay, UI, physics, shader, optimisation, porting, VR

Source Control Git (Git commands, GitHub, GitLab, SourceTree)

Project Planning Trello, Jira, Confluence, HacknPlan, ClickUp

MS Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook

Personal Skills

Problem solving

Mentorship

Customer service

• Project management

Communication

Teamwork

Autonomy

• Multilingual: English, Indonesian, Japanese

Professional Experience

Unreal Engine Developer @ Tabcorp (Full-Time)

July 2023 – Present

I work on the development of a racing simulation graphics engine using C++ within Unreal Engine.

Unreal Engine C++ Programmer @ Blowfish Studios (Full-Time)

Sep 2021 – May 2023

I developed video game projects using Unreal Engine and C++, and also helped external developers port their games to PC and consoles.

Game Design Workshop Instructor @ Dr Egg Adventures (Contract)

Jun 2021 – Jul 2021

I taught primary school kids on game design basics using various apps through Zoom.

IT Support Staff @ National Institute of Dramatic Arts (Casual)

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

I served as level 1 & 2 IT support for students and staffs within the Kensington campus.

General Finance Officer @ Rider & Bell Group (Full-Time)

Jul 2018 - Oct 2019

I performed various financial affairs tasks including general bookkeeping, goods delivery management and supply purchasing management, along with occasional odd tasks such as low-level IT support and website maintenance.

Private Tutor @ Ezy Math Tutoring (Contract)

Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

I worked as a contractor for a private tutoring agency for which I prepared my own content.

Education

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

2019 - 2020

Advanced Diploma of Game Programming

University of New South Wales

2014 - 2018

Bachelor of Economics

Caringbah High School

2008 - 2013

Higher School Certificate

References

Richard Delamore

Patrick Tedesco

richard.delamore@tabcorp.com.au

patrick.tedesco123@gmail.com

Senior Unreal Programmer @ Tabcorp

Publishing Producer @ Blowfish Studios